(Bernadette:)(phone rings)
(Howard:)You need to take that?
(Stuart:)It's just my dad,
probably calling
(Stuart:)to wish me a happy birthday.
(Stuart:)I'll call him back.
(Stuart:)You were saying?
(Emily:)Look, Raj, be honest with me.
(Emily:)If you want to end things,
just do it.
(Emily:)Don't expect me
to do it for you.
(Raj:)End things? I'm trying to
tell you that I love you.
BOTH:
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
(Penny:)Wow, there's
a Denny's in Vegas
(Penny:)you can actually
get married in.
(chuckles)
Doesn't sound
very romantic.
(Penny:)Yeah, but we could get
heart-shaped pancakes.
(Leonard:)I'm sure we'll find
a decent chapel.
(Penny:)Yeah.
This is crazy!
I know!
(Leonard:)You think people
are gonna be mad?